Hello Friends.
Today we are going to talk about
why you should become a health agent at ICC Lombard?  Imagine
if suddenly you have to go to the hospital and
getting a bill of 5 to 7 lakhs is not a big deal
and in such a situation a health insurance
agent not only provides a policy but
saves the family from financial shock but the question is
whether the income of ICC Labord Health Agent is
stable or not, you
will also know about this and whether I can
work from Delhi, Lucknow, Chennai, Kolkata or Maharashtra
or not, I will try to explain this also to you in this video, this
live.
In today's live I am going to clear all your
doubts which you have to
watch carefully.  I am Yogendra
Verma, Recruitment Manager, IC Labard and
today we will talk about the
career, income and future of ICC Labard General Health Insurance in a very
practical way.
So why did ICC become a Labard Health agent?
ICU LMB is a strong and trusted brand.  The
company
's experience, claim handling and system are
quite mature in the health insurance segment.  The most important things for an agent are
customer trust, claim
support and long term business.  This is what
makes ICICI Lombard agent friendly.   That's
why people become agents with ICIC LBD.  Should I
talk about the health insurance segment
, is it a growth sector or not?  So
in simple language, health insurance is the
fastest growing insurance
segment in India.  Medical inflation is increasing every day.
Lifestyle diseases are becoming common.
People want cashless treatment.  No one
wants to go for the reimbursement option.
That is why today health insurance has
become a compulsory need, not an option.  That is why
joining the health insurance sector will be useful for you.   Let me
talk about whether this is a job or a business, I will
answer you in very simple words, this is a
very important question, ICC Lombard
Health Agent is not a job, it is an
independent business, here you are your own boss, there is
no income limit, you keep getting
renewable income and long term
asset is created which
takes you to the next level,
this is the best model for those who want freedom and growth,
which you always have to keep in mind, is it
possible to do both full time or part time?   Yes, this
is absolutely possible.  You can
join it as a part time basis along with your job
or you
can work here on a part time basis with any of your businesses.   If
you are a housewife, retired professional
, fresher or student, you can still
join this working.  You can
start according to your time.
How much commission do you get?  This is a very important
question.  So in health insurance the agent
gets 15% to 35% commission and renewal
commission is 15%.  I am
talking about ICC Lombard.  As your
portfolio grows, passive
income is created.  Renewable income keeps
increasing.  For which people join this business.   The
exact structure is clearly explained at the time of joining.  Whether
the income is
stable or not.  So,
in starting, efforts are required, hard work is required and
on a sincere note, you will have to participate in learning and training.
But renewal income every two to three years
gives you financial stability and predictable cash flow.
So that you can generate a long lasting
study income.  That is why
many people choose it as a long term career.
What is the joining process?
So that is also very simple.  In the joining process,
you have to bring your basic list of
documents which I have mentioned here
or if you WhatsApp me, I will
send it to you.  You will then have to train for an exam.  You will have to appear for the
IRD exam, the
fee for which will be ₹1000 and
after passing the exam you will
get the license.  Your code will be generated after you receive your license.
To activate that code,
a policy must be made in the first month.
15,000 premium and 12 policies in a year are
required.  So that your code can continue running.
With proper guidance, this
process becomes smooth and
learning and training will be
available from us on a regular basis from time to time.  Let's talk about the
exam fees and whether the exam is difficult or
not?  So if I talk about exam fees, it is a one-
time fee.  There is an examination fee of ₹1000
which you have to pay until you
pass the exam and the exam is very
simple.  There are objective type question
answers.  There will be 50 question answers.  There will be
four answers for one question.
You can pass out by tick marking and you have to score
15 marks.  If you
get 15 marks out of 50 then you pass your exam.
If the training is given properly then the exam is
cleared easily and there is
no tension.  Let's talk about
how much training is required and what type it is.  So let
me tell you that training is not just for exams.  There are also a
wide range of health insurance
products to learn about.  Working is done,
claim process is done.  Many things are
taught.  What is covered in the training?
It will include understanding of health products
, claim process,
sales approach, customer handling,
practical market scenarios and
many digital marketing steps
that will upgrade you.  The training
continues step by step.
Through Zoom Meetings and Microsoft
through Microsoft Teams.  You
can join us all over India.
What are common myths about agents?
People who are about to join this business have
some fear,
myth, misconception in their mind as if they will
not get the claim.  Secondly, only those with
contacts are successful.
Third, insurance is not resectable in selling.  Do
n't keep this wrong myth in your mind.   The
reality is that the agents who work with the right product and right
guidance are
definitely successful in the long term and
continuous learning and training
upgrades you and takes you forward so that
you do not become negative. Many people ask,
like I am Yogendra Verma in Delhi
and you can be in Lucknow, Chennai, Kolkata,
Maharashtra or any corner of India,
then how will you get support,
today the insurance business is
not location dependent, or let me
clarify to you, everything is done online
onboarding.  ZM training takes place.
WhatsApp support is available.  We
provide it through digital.  You
can work in any corner of India.  There is no
challenge or issue of any kind.  The next
question people ask is
can freshers join?  So,
for success in insurance, knowledge is
more important than degree.  Learning
Mindset.  You must have time.   There should be a
learning mindset.  There should be consistency.  You
should have ethics and
you should be able to communicate what you are taught to people.  If you
talk to people as much as possible and work hard, you will get
results.  This is the power for this
business.  Any fresher or
experienced person can join in this.
Why is joining ICC Nobody a better option
?  Number one, its biggest reason is better
trusted brand.  The biggest and best
trusted brand.  Health insurance has a
strong health portfolio.  It
is a process driven system.  The
company owns long term credibility.  Due to which
people want to join IC Labard.
This is a safe and respected choice for an agent's career.   I will
talk to you.  If you also want a career
where hard work pays off in the
long term and where you can
help people and also earn income, then
ICC Lombard Health Insurance
Agent is the best option.  My name is
Yogendra Verma Recruitment Manager you
can WhatsApp me.  You can call.  The
number is given below 981826521
Write JOIN in the comment or directly WhatsApp it, you will
get correct guidance without false
promises. Hello friends, thank you for
this YouTube live, thank you, thank you so
much.